testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi.
This is the sofa.
Sofa.
Something like that.
I was taking selfies earlier and I really liked the natural light so I
turned on the live. I thought I'd just do a quick one.
I didn't put on any makeup today.
It's been a while since I went bare-faced. And today for the first time in a while in the morning
I did go to work out but anyway it's a day for me to stay home.
I'm so happy today. I'm just so happy.
Like how long has it been since I had a full day off.
I was originally going to go to Hyehwa today but yesterday was a public holiday so
they had all the performances yesterday. So there were barely any performances today so I thought well
I should just rest what else can I do. I should go on a day like this though.
My feelings for you keep growing without me knowing
Ah you guys are 7 hours behind right now so
Behind or ahead I'm not sure
Is Europe earlier? No wait we're more to the east
right? We're a bit earlier.
We're ahead right? Right? Right? Ah I'm confused. Anyway so
What was I talking about? If we're ahead then 7 hours
behind means you must have just woken up. You probably just woke up
and are getting ready for school right? Out of all of them only one has class
starting now and the other one doesn't? I think it starts this week this year
But well no. They said they were going on a trip so
I guess not. Then I'll do a video call later today and while we're on the call
we decided to choose our accommodation. No wait it's not night time yet
so this song doesn't fit. Ah
Wait I need to turn off noise canceling.
You said I need to do this with noise canceling off right?
How do I do this? Someone said turning off noise canceling makes the sound
clearer but how do I turn it off.
I listened to it the day before yesterday too and the song sounded a bit
like the audio was breaking.
Can you hear me well? It's not breaking. It is breaking a little bit though.
Go into Bluetooth settings
Why isn't it working? Where and what should I look for?
Mic audio control center in the control center
How do I do this?
Voice isolation.
It's already turned off.
Voice isolation is off what is this why is it like this
Whatever I don't know.
It's really windy today. I think it was a good idea not to go out.
I just put on makeup because I was bored.
Wednesday feels somewhat clean.
I heard the flu is going around. Yeah it is. We have to be careful.
The perfume I'm wearing today is
something comfortable
Ah I feel like something just hit me
The weather is really so nice.
Right now this river and that tower in front of me
Is that a tower? Namsan Tower anyway it's so pretty.
It's not exactly a Han River view but wait is this the Han River?
A river in Korea is the Han River I guess.
I haven't had lunch yet so I ordered Subway. When is it
coming? I'm going to turn this off when the Subway gets here.
They said this is clothes where you stand the collar up like this.
I don't know. These days people
wear it like this a lot I guess.
Look at my hair volume.
How do I look today? How's my condition?
Today I look a bit
I wanted to turn this on in landscape mode on the right but if I
turn it on in landscape mode I have to hold it like this so my face
will just keep looking wide so
I'm pretending to be the prettiest person in the world right now.
Joint lives don't work on Fromm. I want to do a Fromm joint live too. Actually
Jiwon unnie went over to Hayoung unnie's house the other day.
Why didn't they invite me? I was
alone back then too.
Why didn't they invite me?
Flover is there any content you want to see again
on our channel?
I feel like we've done everything you guys wanted to see. We did horror too and
we did Dangerous Invitation. Something we haven't done.
Fromm-bokki
Karaoke. Ah but honestly for things like Tray Karaoke I feel like
getting hit by the tray is funny of course but in my opinion
the seniors' chemistry and the seniors being genuinely funny is what really saved that content.
The seniors were just so funny.
Something that's funny and entertaining even if we don't try to be funny.
You know what I mean? Like Dangerous Invitation where we
don't necessarily have to make jokes or at least
not full-on comedy but something that's funny even if we don't try.
Jiheon shoots? Who is it? Hey I can't do mental math. I'm really
terrible at mental math.
That's just telling me to pay for it. Hey that's just an excuse to make me pay.
I have no money these days.
Driving practice. Ah I can't practice driving because
it would be fine if it was just me but I'm worried I might sacrifice innocent citizens.
Let's do Bbang-chongmu Shoots. Bbang-chongmu Shoots. Hayoung unnie will pay for it.
Going to the countryside for a popularity test. Ah we definitely can't do that.
Who would know us?
Ah we've tried almost everything so now
Wow there's really a lot you guys want to see. The chat is so fast. I can't even read it.
But for things like Muhan Company you know. Honestly our
members are bad at skits. Like we have to act out a skit but we keep breaking character
and instead of calling them boss we keep going ah unnie
unnie like this and the member who's especially bad at it is Chaeyoung unnie she's really
bad at it.
She just breaks character.
Like this is a company unnie you're at a
company right now. Our members
might actually make that funny but skits are
just too hard for us. Since we haven't experienced
company life maybe that's why? No wait. The seniors didn't
experience it either so how were they so good at it?
Nametag ripping or something like 2 Days & 1 Night
where we really
sleep outside.
What was that show? Family Outing. Something like that.
Fromm-bokki.
Even just doing Fromm-bokki would be funny.
Or guessing when it's going to snow
Snowball fights ah.
Ah so what should we film
these days so you guys would like it? There are actually way more people watching it
than I thought. Right?
Or how about this?
Not knowing how much is left on the card. This is also something they did on Infinity Challenge but
you don't know how much is on the card and
we take turns spending money and the person who gets the limit exceeded error at the end
has to pay for everything.
If I don't get caught what should I buy?
Should I buy a PlayStation?
Buy a car you say. That's just telling me to buy it for you.
What else is there? Or should we go with Infinity Challenge?
Infinity Challenge
But the Infinity Challenge seniors were just genuinely so funny right?
And the scale is huge. Infinity Challenge. Here you go.
Unnie's Temptation
Ah this too though the seniors were just so funny that even watching them
talk in the meeting room is hilarious.
Oh right. It's here I should go get it. How about Bad Brothers?
Ah I'm too lazy. It'll turn off on its own right?
Turn off.
Quiet.
How about Bad Brothers? Bad Sisters
We do Bad Sisters. But what if everyone just dumps everything
on me?
I feel like everything will come to me since I'm the maknae.
Our feelings are already hurt.
Or maybe
Reading fortunes or face reading. Ah we already did that on our channel.
A telepathy special sounds good.
I like it. A telepathy special special.
Telepathy special is good. We should do that. How about it?
Or catch the tail.
I don't think nametag ripping will work. Because for nametag ripping you need at least
ten people right? So nametag ripping probably won't work and
catch the tail
For the Bangkok special the writer was the one who was super funny.
We need people like that to come out but
Catch the tail sounds good though.
Or something that idol groups used to do
a lot in the past like
a guerrilla fan meeting.
Guerrilla concert.
But Flovers who didn't know about it would be so upset right?
Flovers in the countryside wouldn't be able to see it.
You want to see Punch? I want to see him too but he's not at my house right now.
He's at my parents' house.
Catch the tail or telepathy sound good. You're Beautiful.
You're Beautiful.
Nagyung unnie would get first place of course. She's our visual center.
Myungsoo is 12 years old. Hayoung is 12 years old.
Hayoung is 12 years old would be cute too right?
That's good. But what are 12-year-olds like these days?
12-year-olds these days are scary too.
I've made up my mind.
Catch the tail or telepathy or Hayoung is 12 years old
Or
Jung Chongmu Shoots.
I think we have to go with Jung. Because he was Jung Chongmu.
I think going with Jung Chongmu Shoots sounds a bit better.
Changing it from Jung to Heon right now would
mean changing both the first and last consonants so
Chongmu Shoots.
I should go get my Subway. The weather is cold these days so I'm wearing this. Bye.
I'm going to go now. It's been 32 minutes so
I'll be on my way now.
Bye.
I'll do Tiramisu Cake one last time for you.
Tiramisu Cake. I suddenly got into this song lately.
Why is that? I was watching Shorts and the intro came up and
it suddenly reminded me of the old days so
The person who approached me silently like a light
There was a challenge for this but I don't remember what it was I only remember this part
Your face filling up my mind for a moment
Even if I try to be brave
My feelings for you keep growing
without me knowing
I'll be going now. Flover.
Okay? Have a delicious dinner. Okay?